Oh, it's like someone
sawed a cow in half.
My father's a gynecologist,
I think I can handle it.
(Raj:)And, now I'm gay.
(Bernadette:)You know, I was thinking,
(Bernadette:)without Sheldon most of us
would have never met,
(Bernadette:)but Penny would still
live across from him.
(Amy:)And with Leonard out of the picture,
(Amy:)we all know what that would mean.
(Penny:)We do?
(Penny:)Hey, Sheldon.
(Stuart:)Hello.
(Penny:)Doing laundry?
(Sheldon:)Of course I'm doing laundry.
(Sheldon:)Saturday night is laundry night,
(Sheldon:)and I'm in a laundry room, so...
(Sheldon:)I believe your inference is justified.
(Penny:)My inference is justified.
(Penny:)Sheldon, you are so funny.
(Penny:)Anyway, I need to do my laundry, too,
(Penny:)because these clothes are so dirty.